{
    "subject": "resource/Paulo_Moura",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Rio_de_Janeiro",
    "human_readable": "Paulo Moura died in Rio de Janeiro.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8997821807861328,
            "question": "Is there any historical context related to Paulo Moura's death in Rio de Janeiro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8755786418914795,
            "question": "Was Paulo Moura born in Rio de Janeiro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8566890358924866,
            "question": "Where did Paulo Moura die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7021107077598572,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Paulo Moura died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5630195140838623,
            "question": "Is there any information about Paulo Moura's life besides his death location?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5378492474555969,
            "question": "What was Paulo Moura known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4860866963863373,
            "question": "Were there any significant events in Paulo Moura's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45034873485565186,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Paulo Moura?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36666443943977356,
            "question": "Do you know anything about Paulo Moura's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.354823499917984,
            "question": "Are there any records or documents about Paulo Moura's life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paulo Moura died in Rio de Janeiro.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6894_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything about Paulo Moura's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6894_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Paulo Moura?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6894_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant events in Paulo Moura's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6894_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6894_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple reports stating that Paulo Moura died after a fight against cancer, and all of them mention that he was receiving treatment for lymphoma at a clinic in Rio de Janeiro. This information supports the triple statement that Paulo Moura died in Rio de Janeiro."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Paulo Moura died at the S\u00e3o Vicente clinic in Rio de Janeiro, which supports the statement that he died in Rio de Janeiro."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}